Semmler, Alexander; Papers mss131
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Chamber Music, 1940-1977; Undated; 3; 2.98 cubic ft.
  - Opus 45: Meditation and Capriccio for Flute and Piano (also arranged for Oboe or Clarinet and Piano), Undated; genreform: Manuscript flute part (Box 2 (3-Chamber Music), Folder 54-55)
  - Opus 45: Meditation and Capriccio for Flute and Piano (also arranged for Oboe or Clarinet and Piano), Undated; genreform: Manuscript clarinet part (Box 2 (3-Chamber Music), Folder 56)
  - Opus 47: Quintet for Bassoon and String Quartet, Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score and parts (Oversized 9, Folder 9)
- Instrumental Works without an Opus Number, 1916-1964; Undated; 4; 1.49 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  This series consists of those instrumental works written by Alexander Semmler under his own name that were never assigned an opus number by him. Included in this series is a collection of instrumental works that seems to date from Semmler's youth; this was entitled "Alexander Semmler: Early Instrumental Pieces" by the archivist. These materials are all in German, with Italian notations. Another work in this series is Semmler's "Entre dos Luces", for violin and string orchestra, which is in Spanish with Italian notations. All other materials in this series are in English with Italian notations. Also included in this series are the "Calendar Sketches," music written for sale to home-movie makers to accompany their films. The compositions are accompanied by a typescript describing the purpose of the music and suggesting uses for each piece. It is unclear whether this was written by Semmler.
  - [Alexander Semmler: Early Instrumental Pieces], 1916; genreform: Manuscript score (Oversized 10, Folder 1)
  - Along the Sawkill, 1959; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 10, Folder 2)
  - Buddy Taylor's Concerto, 1948; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 1)
  - [Calendar Sketches], Undated; genreform: Typescript description and suggestions (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 2)
  - [Calendar Sketches], 1956; genreform: Pieces 1-14: Manuscript score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 3-6)
  - Commercial Music for Celesta and Piano, 1964; genreform: "Brisk Movement, Industrial, etc.": Typed index and manuscript score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 7)
  - Commercial Music for Celesta and Piano, 1964; genreform: "Dramatic Character Pieces" and "Lyrical Pieces": Typed index and manuscript score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 8)
  - Commercial Music for Celesta and Piano, 1964; genreform: Ink sketches with titles (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 9)
  - Commercial Music for Celesta and Piano, Undated; genreform: Pencil sketches with titles (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 10)
  - Commercial Music for Celesta and Piano, Undated; genreform: Pencil sketches without titles (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 11)
  - Concert Waltz for Piano, Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Oversized 10, Folder 3)
  - Duets for Strings in the First Position: Playable for Two Violins or Violin and Viola or Violin and Cello, 1964; genreform: Manuscript full score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 12)
  - Duets for Strings in the First Position: Playable for Two Violins or Violin and Viola or Violin and Cello, 1964; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 10, Folder 4)
  - Entre dos Luces: Fantasia para Violino y Orquesta de Cuerdas, 1954; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 13)
  - Entre dos Luces: Fantasia para Violino y Orquesta de Cuerdas, 1954; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score and parts (Oversized 10, Folder 5)
  - [Four Orchestral Pieces], 1960; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 10, Folder 6)
  - Idyl for Piano, 1938; genreform: Manuscript score (Oversized 10, Folder 7)
  - Improvisation for Guitar: To Jeanne and Jacob Andonian, 1957; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 14)
  - Improvisation for Guitar: To Jeanne and Jacob Andonian, 1957; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 10, Folder 8)
  - Improvisations for Piano, Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 15)
  - Improvisations for Piano, Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 10, Folder 9)
  - Minuet, Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Oversized 10, Folder 10)
  - Mount Overlook, 1959; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 10, Folder 11)
  - Music for Recorder, 1952; genreform: Dance for Sopranino Recorder and Piano: Manuscript score and recorder part (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 16)
  - Music for Recorder, 1952; genreform: Lullaby for Sopranino Recorder and Piano: Manuscript score and recorder part (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 17)
  - Music for Recorder, Undated; genreform: Autumn Pastoral: Onionskin manuscript score and manuscript parts (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 18)
  - Music for Recorder, Undated; genreform: [Pencil Sketches for Recorder]: Manuscript sketches (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 19)
  - Nocturne for Flute, Viola, and Harp, Undated; genreform: Manuscript flute part (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 20)
  - Nocturne for Flute, Viola, and Harp, Undated; genreform: Manuscript viola part (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 21)
  - Nocturne for Flute, Viola, and Harp, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 22)
  - Nocturne for Flute, Viola, and Harp, Undated; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 10, Folder 12)
  - Nocturne for Flute, Viola, and Harp, Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score, flute part, and viola part (Oversized 10, Folder 13)
  - Nocturne for Orchestra and Piano, Undated; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 10, Folder 14)
  - Pastoral(e) for Solo Oboe and Strings, Undated; genreform: Manuscript piano/oboe score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 23)
  - Pastoral(e) for Solo Oboe and Strings, Undated; genreform: Manuscript oboe part (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 24)
  - Pastoral(e) for Solo Oboe and Strings, Undated; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 11, Folder 1)
  - Pastoral(e) for Solo Oboe and Strings, Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript piano/oboe score (Oversized 11, Folder 2)
  - [Piano Pieces], Undated; genreform: Bound manuscript score (Oversized 11, Folder 3)
  - Prairie Sunset for Harp Solo, Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 25)
  - Prairie Sunset for Harp Solo, Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 11, Folder 4)
  - Rush Hour, Undated; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 11, Folder 5)
  - Six Easy Pieces for Piano, Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Oversized 11, Folder 6)
  - Solemn Epilogue [for Concert Band], Undated; genreform: Manuscript piano reduction (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 26)
  - Solemn Epilogue [for Concert Band], Undated; genreform: Manuscript woodwind parts (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 27)
  - Solemn Epilogue [for Concert Band], Undated; genreform: Manuscript brass parts (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 28)
  - Solemn Epilogue [for Concert Band], Undated; genreform: Manuscript percussion parts (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 29)
  - Solemn Epilogue [for Concert Band], Undated; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 11, Folder 7)
  - Sonatina for Flute and Harp, 1958; genreform: Manuscript full score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 30)
  - Space Cadets March, Undated; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 11, Folder 8)
  - Thirty Easy Duets for Alto Recorder, Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 31)
  - Thirty Easy Duets for Alto Recorder, Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 11, Folder 9)
  - Tonal Canvases 1959: Musical Impressions of an Art Exhibit, ca. 1959; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 11, Folder 10)
  - Twilight Melody, 1959; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 11, Folder 11)
  - Two American Indian Scenes, Undated; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 11, Folder 12)
  - Voodeko: A 20th Century Primitive Dance for Concert Band, Undated; genreform: Manuscript piano reduction (Box 3 (4-Instrumental Works without an Opus ), Folder 32)
  - Voodeko: A 20th Century Primitive Dance for Concert Band, Undated; genreform: Manuscript full score (Oversized 11, Folder 13)
  - Voodeko: A 20th Century Primitive Dance for Concert Band, Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript piano reduction (Oversized 11, Folder 14)
- Vocal and Choral Music, 1914-1968; Undated; 5; 0.82 cubic ft.
  This series consists of the vocal and choral works written by Alexander Semmler under his own name. The arrangement of this series is alphabetical except in the case of those works to which Semmler assigned opus numbers; they are arranged under 'O' in numerical order. Please note that the items in Oversized Folder 1 are all in German. All other items are in English, except for some song lyrics in Spanish. Where there is no notation to the contrary, both words and music are presumed to be by Semmler. In all other cases, the lyricist's name is listed first.
  - [Alexander Semmler: Early Songs, Sketches, and Miscellanea], 1914-1919; genreform: Manuscript scores, sketches, and drafts; printed music by August Brunetti-Pisano and Armin Knab; correspondence (Oversized 12, Folder 1)
  - The Challenge, Undated; genreform: Manuscript score; manuscript and typed lists of timings (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 33)
  - The Challenge, Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Day in the Morning: For Unaccompanied Mixed Chorus (J. Shotwell/Semmler), 1957; genreform: Printed score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 34)
  - Four Madrigals (The Seasons): Arranged for Mixed Voices (SATB), 1965; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 35)
  - Four Madrigals (The Seasons): Arranged for Mixed Voices (SATB) and for Male Voices (TTBB), 1965; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 3)
  - Four Madrigals (The Seasons): Arranged for Male Voices (TTBB), Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 36)
  - Full of Wonder: A Musical Christmas Play (Lund and Semmler/Semmler), 1954; genreform: Bound manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 4)
  - Full of Wonder: A Musical Christmas Play (Lund and Semmler/Semmler), 1954; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 5)
  - The Hills (I. Semmler/A. Semmler), Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 37)
  - The Hills (I. Semmler/A. Semmler), Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 6)
  - "I knew it all along", Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 38)
  - Lullaby (H. Shotwell): Arranged for Solo and for Mixed Voices by A. Semmler, Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 7)
  - Opus 24: Chamber Music (Divertimento) for Mixed Voices (Four Parts) and Harp (or Piano), 1954; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 39)
  - Opus 24: Chamber Music (Divertimento) for Mixed Voices (Four Parts) and Harp (or Piano), 1954; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 8)
  - Opus 24: Chamber Music (Divertimento) for Mixed Voices (Four Parts) and Harp (or Piano), Undated; genreform: Manuscript bass part (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 40)
  - Opus 30: [Seven Songs for Medium Voice]: La Desierta Plaza (Machado/Semmler); Renacimiento (Machado/Semmler), 1954; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 41)
  - Opus 30: [Seven Songs for Medium Voice]: La Desierta Plaza (Machado/Semmler); Renacimiento (Machado/Semmler); Respice (J. Shotwell/Semmler); Time is a Cunning Thief (J. Shotwell/Semmler); Viewpoint Cocktail; The Chicken (Morganstern/Semmler); Nightfall (S, ca. 1954-1955; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 9)
  - Opus 30: [Seven Songs for Medium Voice]: Respice (J. Shotwell/Semmler); Time is a Cunning Thief (J. Shotwell/Semmler), Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 42)
  - Opus 30: [Seven Songs for Medium Voice]: Viewpoint Cocktail; The Chicken (Morganstern/Semmler), 1955; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 43)
  - The Owl and the Pussy-Cat: For Chorus of Mixed Voices (SATB) with Piano Accompaniment (Lear/Semmler), 1950; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 10)
  - The Owl and the Pussy-Cat: For Chorus of Mixed Voices (SATB) with Piano Accompaniment (Lear/Semmler), 1967; genreform: Printed score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 44)
  - Prelude and Hymn: A Voice-Instrumental for Mixed Chorus a capella, 1964; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 45)
  - Prelude and Hymn: A Voice-Instrumental for Mixed Chorus a capella, 1964; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 11)
  - Sinfonia Abstracta for Male Voices, 1968; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 46)
  - Sinfonia Abstracta for Male Voices, 1968; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 12)
  - Sing Along!, 1958; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 47)
  - "There's a city by the river", Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 13)
  - Three Christmas Songs for Mixed Voices a capella (E. Semmler/A. Semmler), Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 48)
  - Three Christmas Songs for Mixed Voices a capella (E. Semmler/A. Semmler), Undated; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 14)
  - Vee Double U (Volkswagen Theme), 1967; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 49)
  - Vee Double U (Volkswagen Theme), 1967; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 15)
  - "We are players all upon the stage of chance", Undated; genreform: Manuscript score; pencil sketches on back (Box 3 (5-Vocal and Choral Music), Folder 50)
- Music Written as Ralph Sandor, 1940-1950; Undated; 6; 0.2 cubic ft.
  This series includes music written by Alexander Semmler under the name Ralph Sandor (or Zandor). Much of it is more commercially oriented than his other works. This series includes both instrumental and vocal music. As with the vocal music written by Semmler under his own name, when there is a lyricist's name given, it is listed first.
  - Entre dos Luces (Twilight): Tango, 1950; genreform: Onionskin manuscript score (Oversized 12, Folder 16)
  - Incidental Music: Piano or Organ, 1941; genreform: Printed score (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 51)
  - Incidental Music: Piano or Organ, Book II, 1944; genreform: Printed score (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 52)
  - Light Orchestral Music, Undated; genreform: Manuscript string parts (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 53-54)
  - Light Orchestral Music, Undated; genreform: Manuscript woodwind parts (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 55)
  - Light Orchestral Music, Undated; genreform: Manuscript brass parts (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 56)
  - Light Orchestral Music, Undated; genreform: Manuscript percussion parts (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 57)
  - Light Orchestral Music, Undated; genreform: Manuscript harp part (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 58)
  - Light Orchestral Music, Undated; genreform: Manuscript piano part (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 59)
  - Pop Music, Undated; genreform: Manuscript scores and sketches for instrumental and vocal works (lyrics for vocal works by Sandor and by Alice Blackburn) (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 60)
  - Tangos by Sandor, Undated; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 61)
  - [Three Pieces by Ralph Sandor: "Oh You Gypsy!" (Blackburn/Sandor); Maracaibo; "Out of the Gray" (Ball/Sandor)], 1940; genreform: Manuscript score; printed score (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 62)
  - [Violin and Piano Music], 1941; genreform: Manuscript score (Box 3 (6-Music Written as Ralph Sandor), Folder 63)
- Sketches and Notebooks, 1919-1954; Undated; 7; 3.63 cubic ft.
  Arranged in two subseries, the first consisting of manuscript sketches and the second of notebooks. The sketches are arranged alphabetically by folder title; the notebooks are arranged first alphabetically by title and then chronologically. When a folder bore more than one title, the archivist chose the spine title to represent the whole, with any other titles given after a semicolon. Titles that Semmler crossed out were not included in the folder title. Photocopies of Semmler's original folders were included in each folder. Included in this series is "Queen Mystery Cue #12", a piece by Bernard Herrmann originally written for the CBS radio drama "Ellery Queen."
  This series includes manuscript sketches and notebooks.
  - Sketches, 1919-1954; Undated; 7.1
    - Bassoon Quintet (Sketches); [Instrumental and Vocal Sketches], 1939; 1943-1944; Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 13, Folder 1)
    - Chamber Music: Mixed Voices and Harp or Piano (Opus 24); Lullaby; [Sketches], Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 13, Folder 2)
    - Complete Pieces, 1944; Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches; typewritten lyrics (Oversized 13, Folder 3)
    - Concertino for Piano and Orchestra (Sketches); [Radio Cues], 1939; Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 14, Folder 1)
    - Counterpointal Sketches; Melodic Writing (Single Lines), 1940; 1942; 1952; Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 14, Folder 2)
    - Cue Sketches: CBS Recording, Dec 47, 1947; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 14, Folder 3)
    - Don Quixote, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 14, Folder 4)
    - [Early Instrumental and Vocal Sketches; Dance Music Sketches], 1919; 1921; 1927; Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 15, Folder 1)
    - Farmer in the Dell: A Caprice for Piano and String Orchestra (Sandor), Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 15, Folder 2)
    - For the Sound-track, 1946; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 15, Folder 3)
    - Foundation Play (Wood/Semmler), Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 15, Folder 4)
    - Light Industrials (Harry Glass Recording 59); [Indian Rhapsody], Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 15, Folder 5)
    - Manhattan Diary, Orchestra Sketches, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 16, Folder 1)
    - Mary Brown, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches; manuscript and typed lyrics, scenario, and script pages (Oversized 16, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Commercial Pieces (Material), Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 16, Folder 3)
    - Mood Sketches, 1946; Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 16, Folder 4)
    - [My Country [,] 'Tis America (Ralph Sandor); Twelve Tone Rows and Untitled Sketches], 1940; Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 16, Folder 5)
    - Odes to Darkness; Current Sketches, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 16, Folder 6)
    - Patriotic Songs, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 16, Folder 7)
    - Progressive Jazz, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 16, Folder 8)
    - Recordings Musicana U. S. A., Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 17, Folder 1)
    - Rias Symphony, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 17, Folder 2)
    - Serious Sketches; Nocturne (Manhattan); Old Dances in New Style; [Sketches], 1929; 1931; 1941; 1944; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 17, Folder 3)
    - Sight-Singing, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 18, Folder 1)
    - Sketches in Progress; H. C. Quartet, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 18, Folder 2)
    - String Quartet Sketches; Symphony 1st Movement; [Artistic and Commercial Sketches], 1939; 1946; 1954; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 18, Folder 3)
    - Suite for Orchestra etc., 1933; 1938; 1946; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 18, Folder 4)
    - Symphony No. 2 (Sinfonietta No. 2); Horizons, Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 19, Folder 1)
    - Theme and Variations: Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, 1946; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 19, Folder 2)
    - Theme and Variations for Orchestra; [Vocal Music], 1938; 1941; Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 19, Folder 3)
    - ["To Charly;" On the High Seas; Pixies], Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 19, Folder 4)
    - Various Sketches: Fugues, Inventions, etc., 1943; 1944; Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 19, Folder 5)
    - Violin Concerto, 1948; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 19, Folder 6)
    - [Vocal Sketches and Notes], Undated; genreform: Manuscript sketches (Oversized 19, Folder 7)
  - Notebooks, 1937-1950; Undated; 7.2
    - Loose sketches, notes, and miscellanea, Undated (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 1)
    - Classical Themes; Yankee Doodle [et al.], Undated (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 2)
    - Duet Cl. And Fl. [et al.]; Piano Prelude [et al.], 1941; Undated (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 3)
    - Madrigals; Original Themes, Undated (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 4)
    - Prelude and Hymn; Valse; Primitive Dance from Dance Suite, Undated (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 5)
    - Rhythmic Studies; Valentino Sketches: Cl., Bssn., Fl. Solos, Undated (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 6)
    - Sinfonietta, beg.; War Commercials etc., Undated (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 7)
    - Untitled notebooks, 1937-1938 (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 8)
    - Untitled notebooks, 1938 (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 9)
    - Untitled notebooks, 1938-1939 (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 10)
    - Untitled notebooks, 1939 (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 11)
    - Untitled notebooks, 1941; 1946 (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 12)
    - Untitled notebooks, 1946; 1950 (Box 4 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 13)
    - Untitled, undated notebooks (Box 5 (7-Sketches and Notebooks), Folder 1-13)